So as an artist, I get most of my ideas, not most of, but like I get a lot of my ideas
in the space between asleep and awake, or sometimes even just like as I'm asleep and
then I wake up in the middle of the night with ideas.
And right now I'm working on music.
So before I went to bed, I said, let me listen to this thing that I'm working on because
I need to check it out to see like if I like it.
So I did a one woman show last year called What Would the Ancestors Say?
And then I made it into a book and there's a song in the show called Stardust.
And I decided to try to do a remix of Stardust.
And so I said, I haven't listened to it in three days.
Now, sometimes you come back to something after three days and you like, the fuck was
that?
Hey, Laurel.
Laurel asked for this earlier.
I think it was Laurel.
So done with that.
June 14th.
Good night.